Guide to the Comic book collection, about 1984-2004.
Comic book collection
- Heckler, 1992; 3 (Box 12)
- Heckler, 1992; 5 (Box 12)
- Heckler, 1992; 6 (Box 12)
- Hellblazer, 1989; 15 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1989; 16 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1989; 17 (Box 13)
  Artist/Penciler: Mike Hoffman
- Hellblazer, 1989; 18 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1989; 19 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1989; 20 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1989; 21 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1989; 22 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1989; 24 (Box 13)
  Artist/Penciler: Ron Tiner
- Hellblazer, 1990; 25 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1990; 26 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1990; 27 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1990; 28 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1990; 29 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1990; 30 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1990; 33 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1990; 34 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1990; 36 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1991; 38 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1991; 39 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1991; 40 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1991; 41 (Box 13)
  Artist/Penciler: Will Simpson
- Hellblazer, 1991; 42 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1991; 43 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1991; 44 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1991; 45 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1991; 46 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1991; 47 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1991; 48 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1992; 49 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1992; 50 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1992; 51 (Box 13)
  Author: John Smith
- Hellblazer, 1992; 52 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1992; 53 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1992; 54 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1992; 55 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1992; 56 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1992; 57 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1992; 58 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1992; 59 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1992; 60 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1993; 61 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1993; 62 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1993; 63 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1993; 64 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1993; 65 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1993; 66 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1993; 67 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1993; 68 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1993; 69 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1993; 70 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1993; 71 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1993; 72 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1994; 73 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1994; 74 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1994; 75 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1994; 76 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1994; 77 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1994; 78 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1994; 79 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1994; 80 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1994; 81 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1994; 82 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1994; 83 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1994; 84 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1995; 85 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1995; 86 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1995; 87 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1995; 88 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1995; 89 (Box 13)
  Author: Paul Jenkins
- Hellblazer, 1995; 90 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1995; 91 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1995; 92 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1995; 93 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1995; 94 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1995; 95 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1995; 96 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1996; 97 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1996; 98 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1996; 99 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1996; 100 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1996; 101 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1996; 102 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1996; 103 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1996; 104 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1996; 105 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1996; 106 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1996; 107 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1996; 108 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1997; 109 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1997; 110 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1997; 111 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1997; 112 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1997; 113 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1997; 114 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1997; 115 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1997; 116 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1997; 117 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1997; 118 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1997; 119 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1997; 120 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1998; 121 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1998; 122 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1998; 123 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1998; 124 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1998; 125 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1998; 126 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 2004; 195 (Box 13)
  Author: Mike Carey
  Artist/Penciler: Leonardo Manco
- Hellblazer, 2004; 196 (Box 13)
  Artist/Penciler: Chris Bruner
- Hellblazer, 2004; 197 (Box 13)
  Artist/Penciler: Marcelo Frusin
- Hellblazer, 2004; 198 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 2004; 199 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 2004; 200 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 2004; 201 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 2005; 202 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 2005; 203 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 2005; 204 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 2005; 205 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 2005; 206 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer, 1993; S1 (Box 13)
- Hellblazer/The Books of Magic, 1997; 1 (Box 13)
  Artist/Penciler: John Ney Rieber
  Notes: two issue limited series cross-over
- Hellblazer/The Books of Magic, 1997; 2 (Box 13)
- Hellboy Christmas Special, 1997; 1 (Box 13)
  Notes: internally numbered #14
- Hellboy: Almost Colossus, 1997; 1 (Box 13)
  Notes: internally numbered #12
- Hellboy: Almost Colossus, 1997; 2 (Box 13)
  Notes: internally numbered #13
- Hellboy: Box full of evil, 1999; 1 (Box 13)
  Notes: internally numbered #15
- Hellboy: Box full of evil, 1999; 2 (Box 13)
  Notes: internally numbered #16
- Hellboy: Conqueror worm, 2002; 1 (Box 13)
  Notes: internally numbered #17
- Hellboy: Conqueror worm, 2002; 2 (Box 13)
  Notes: internally numbered #18
- Hellboy: Conqueror worm, 2002; 3 (Box 13)
  Notes: internally numbered #19
- Hellboy: Conqueror worm, 2002; 4 (Box 13)
  Notes: internally numbered #20
- Hellboy: Seed of destruction, 1994; 1 (Box 13)
  Notes: internally numbered #1
- Hellboy: Seed of destruction, 1994; 2 (Box 13)
  Notes: internally numbered #2
- Hellboy: Seed of destruction, 1994; 3 (Box 13)
  Notes: internally numbered #3
- Hellboy: Seed of destruction, 1994; 4 (Box 13)
  Notes: internally numbered #4
- Hellboy: The corpse and the iron shoes, 1996 (Box 13)
  Notes: internally numbered #6
- Hellboy: The third wish, 2002; 1 (Box 13)
  Notes: internally numbered #21
- Hellboy: The third wish, 2002; 2 (Box 13)
  Notes: internally numbered #22
- Hellboy: Wake the devil, 1997; 1 (Box 13)
  Notes: internally numbered #7
- Hellboy: Wake the devil, 1997; 2 (Box 13)
  Notes: internally numbered #8
- Hellboy: Wake the devil, 1997; 3 (Box 13)
  Notes: internally numbered #9
- Hellboy: Wake the devil, 1997; 4 (Box 13)
  Notes: internally numbered #10
- Hellboy: Wake the devil, 1997; 5 (Box 13)
  Notes: internally numbered #11
- Hellboy: Weird tales, 2003; 1 (Box 13)
  Author: John Cassady
  Artist/Penciler: John Cassady
- Hellboy: Weird tales, 2003; 2 (Box 13)
  Author: Joe Casey
- Hellboy: Weird tales, 2003; 3 (Box 13)
  Author: Alex Maleev
  Artist/Penciler: Alex Maleev
- Hellboy: Weird tales, 2003; 4 (Box 13)
  Artist/Penciler: Roger Langridge
- Hellboy: Weird tales, 2003; 5 (Box 13)
  Author: JH Williams III
  Artist/Penciler: JH Williams III
- Heroes for Hope Starring the X-Men, 1985; 1 (Box 13)
  Author: Alan Moore, Stephen King
- Hieroglyph, 1999; 1 (Box 13)
  Author: Ricardo Delgado
  Artist/Penciler: Ricardo Delgado
- Hieroglyph, 1999; 2 (Box 13)
- Hieroglyph, 1999; 3 (Box 13)
- Hieroglyph, 1999; 4 (Box 13)
- Homelands on the World of Magic: the Gathering, 1996; 1 (Box 13)
  Author: D.G. Chicester
  Publisher: Amalgam/Acclaim
- Horrorist, The, 1995; 1 (Box 13)
  Notes: 2-part miniseries John Constantine
- House of Mystery: Welcome Back to the House of Mystery, 1998; 1 (Box 13)
  Author: Niel Gaiman
  Artist/Penciler: Sergio Aragones
  Notes: compilation featuring multiple artists and writers, framings tory by Neil Gaiman and Sergio Aragones
- House of Secrets, 1996; 1 (Box 13)
- House of Secrets, 1996; 2 (Box 13)
- House of Secrets, 1996; 3 (Box 13)
- House of Secrets, 1997; 4 (Box 13)
- House of Secrets, 1997; 5 (Box 13)
- House of Secrets, 1997; 6 (Box 13)
- House of Secrets, 1997; 7 (Box 13)
- House of Secrets, 1997; 8 (Box 13)
- House of Secrets, 1997; 9 (Box 13)
- House of Secrets, 1997; 10 (Box 13)
- House of Secrets, 1997; 11 (Box 13)
- House of Secrets, 1997; 12 (Box 13)
- House of Secrets, 1997; 13 (Box 13)
- House of Secrets, 1997; 14 (Box 13)
- House of Secrets, 1997; 15 (Box 13)
- House of Secrets, 1997; 16 (Box 13)
- House of Secrets, 1998; 17 (Box 13)
  Artist/Penciler: D'Israeli
- House of Secrets, 1998; 18 (Box 13)
- House of Secrets, 1998; 19 (Box 13)
- House of Secrets, 1998; 20 (Box 13)
- House of Secrets, 1998; 21 (Box 13)
- House of Secrets, 1998; 22 (Box 13)
- House of Secrets, 1998; 23 (Box 13)
- House of Secrets, 1998; 24 (Box 13)
- House of Secrets, 1998; 25 (Box 13)
- House of Secrets: Façade, 1999; 1 (Box 13)
- House of Secrets: Façade, 1999; 2 (Box 13)
- Hunter: The Age of Magic, 2001; 1 (Box 14)
  Author: Dylan Horrocks
- Hunter: The Age of Magic, 2001; 2 (Box 14)
- Hunter: The Age of Magic, 2001; 3 (Box 14)
- Hunter: The Age of Magic, 2001; 4 (Box 14)
- Hunter: The Age of Magic, 2002; 5 (Box 14)
- Hunter: The Age of Magic, 2002; 6 (Box 14)
- Hunter: The Age of Magic, 2002; 7 (Box 14)
  Artist/Penciler: Chris McLoughlin
- Hunter: The Age of Magic, 2002; 8 (Box 14)
- Hunter: The Age of Magic, 2002; 9 (Box 14)
- Hunter: The Age of Magic, 2002; 10 (Box 14)
- Hunter: The Age of Magic, 2002; 11 (Box 14)
- Hunter: The Age of Magic, 2002; 12 (Box 14)
- Hunter: The Age of Magic, 2002; 13 (Box 14)
- Hunter: The Age of Magic, 2002; 14 (Box 14)
- Hunter: The Age of Magic, 2002; 15 (Box 14)
- Hunter: The Age of Magic, 2002; 16 (Box 14)
- Hunter: The Age of Magic, 2003; 17 (Box 14)
- Hunter: The Age of Magic, 2003; 18 (Box 14)
- Hunter: The Age of Magic, 2003; 19 (Box 14)
- Hunter: The Age of Magic, 2003; 20 (Box 14)
- Hunter: The Age of Magic, 2003; 22 (Box 14)
- Hunter: The Age of Magic, 2003; 23 (Box 14)
- Hunter: The Age of Magic, 2003; 24 (Box 14)
- Hunter: The Age of Magic, 2003; 25 (Box 14)
- Iceman, 1984; 1 (Box 14)
  Artist/Penciler: Alan Kupperberg
- Iceman, 1984; 2 (Box 14)
- Iceman, 1984; 3 (Box 14)
- Iceman, 1984; 4 (Box 14)
- Icon, 1993; 1 (Box 14)
  Author: Dwayne McDuffie
  Artist/Penciler: M.D. Bright
- Icon, 1993; 1 (Box 14)
  Notes: Regular ed.
- Identity Crisis, 2004; 1 (Box 14)
  Artist/Penciler: Rags Morales
  Notes: seven issue mini-series
- Identity Crisis, 2004; 2 (Box 14)
- Identity Crisis, 2004; 3 (Box 14)
- Identity Crisis, 2004; 4 (Box 14)
- Identity Crisis, 2004; 5 (Box 14)
- Identity Crisis, 2004; 6 (Box 14)
- Identity Crisis, 2004; 7 (Box 14)
- Immortal Doctor Fate, 1985; 1 (Box 14)
  Author: Martin Pasko
  Artist/Penciler: Walt Simonson
- Immortal Doctor Fate, 1985; 2 (Box 14)
- Immortal Doctor Fate, 1985; 3 (Box 14)
- Impulse, 1995; 1 (Box 14)
- Impulse, 1995; 2 (Box 14)
- Impulse, 1995; 3 (Box 14)
- Impulse, 1995; 4 (Box 14)
- Impulse, 1995; 5 (Box 14)
- Impulse, 1995; 6 (Box 14)
- Impulse, 1995; 7 (Box 14)
  Artist/Penciler: Rick Gnazzo
- Impulse, 1995; 8 (Box 14)
- Impulse, 1995; 9 (Box 14)
- Impulse, 1996; 10 (Box 14)
- Impulse, 1996; 11 (Box 14)
- Impulse, 1996; 12 (Box 14)
- Impulse, 1996; 13 (Box 14)
- Impulse, 1996; 14 (Box 14)
- Impulse, 1996; 15 (Box 14)
- Impulse, 1996; 16 (Box 14)
- Impulse, 1996; 17 (Box 14)
- Impulse, 1996; 18 (Box 14)
- Impulse, 1996; 19 (Box 14)
- Impulse, 1996; 20 (Box 14)
- Impulse, 1997; 21 (Box 14)
  Artist/Penciler: Craig Rousseau
- Impulse, 1997; 22 (Box 14)
- Impulse, 1997; 23 (Box 14)
- Impulse, 1997; 24 (Box 14)
- Impulse, 1997; 25 (Box 14)
- Impulse, 1997; 26 (Box 14)
- Impulse, 1997; 27 (Box 14)
- Impulse, 1997; 28 (Box 14)
- Impulse, 1997; 29 (Box 14)
- Impulse, 1997; 30 (Box 14)
- Impulse, 1997; 31 (Box 14)
- Impulse, 1997; 32 (Box 14)
- Impulse, 1996; Ann. 1 (Box 14)
  Artist/Penciler: Mike Parobeck
- Impulse, 1997; Ann. 2 (Box 14)
- Incredible Hulk, 1971; 140 (Box 14)
  Artist/Penciler: Herb Trimpe
- Industrial Gothic, 1995; 1 (Box 14)
- Industrial Gothic, 1995; 2 (Box 14)
- Industrial Gothic, 1995; 3 (Box 14)
- Industrial Gothic, 1995; 4 (Box 14)
- Industrial Gothic, 1995; 5 (Box 14)
- Inferno, 1997; 1 (Box 14)
  Author: Stuart Immonen
  Notes: Legion of Superheroes spin-off
- Inferno, 1997; 2 (Box 14)
- Inferno, 1998; 3 (Box 14)
- Inferno, 1998; 4 (Box 14)
- Inhumans (v.2), 1998; 2 (Box 14)
  Artist/Penciler: Jae Lee
- Inhumans (v.2), 1999; 3 (Box 14)
- Inhumans (v.2), 1999; 4 (Box 14)
- Inhumans (v.2), 1999; 5 (Box 14)
- Inhumans (v.2), 1999; 6 (Box 14)
- Inhumans (v.2), 1999; 7 (Box 14)
- Inhumans (v.2), 1999; 8 (Box 14)
- Inhumans (v.2), 1999; 9 (Box 14)
- Inhumans (v.2), 1999; 10 (Box 14)
- Inhumans (v.2), 1999; 11 (Box 14)
- Inhumans (v.2), 1999; 12 (Box 14)
- Inhumans (v.3), 2003; 1 (Box 14)
  Author: Sean McKeever
  Artist/Penciler: Matthew Clark
- Inhumans (v.3), 2003; 2 (Box 14)
- Inhumans (v.4), 2003; 1 (Box 14)
- Inhumans (v.4), 2003; 2 (Box 14)
- Inhumans (v.4), 2003; 3 (Box 14)
- Inhumans (v.4), 2003; 4 (Box 14)
- Instant Piano, 1995; 1 (Box 14)
  Notes: dark horse miniseries 94/95 featuring Kyle Baker, Mark Badger, Robbie Busch, Stephen Destafano, Evan Dorkin
- Instant Piano, 1995; 2 (Box 14)
- Instant Piano, 1995; 3 (Box 14)
- Instant Piano, 1995; 4 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.1), 1994; 1 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.1), 1994; 2 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.1), 1994; 3 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.1), 1994; 4 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.1), 1995; 5 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.1), 1995; 6 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.1), 1995; 7 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.1), 1995; 8 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.1), 1995; 9 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.1), 1995; 10 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.1), 1995; 11 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.1), 1995; 12 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.1), 1995; 13 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.1), 1995; 14 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.1), 1995; 15 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.1), 1995; 16 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.1), 1996; 17 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.1), 1996; 18 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.1), 1996; 19 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.1), 1996; 20 (Box 14)
  Artist/Penciler: Tommy Lee Edwards
- Invisibles (v.1), 1996; 21 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.1), 1996; 22 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.1), 1996; 23 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.1), 1996; 24 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.1), 1996; 25 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.2), 1997; 1 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.2), 1997; 2 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.2), 1997; 3 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.2), 1997; 4 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.2), 1997; 5 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.2), 1997; 6 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.2), 1997; 7 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.2), 1997; 8 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.2), 1997; 9 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.2), 1997; 10 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.2), 1997; 11 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.2), 1998; 12 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.2), 1998; 13 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.2), 1998; 14 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.2), 1998; 15 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.2), 1998; 16 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.2), 1998; 17 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.2), 1998; 18 (Box 14)
  Artist/Penciler: Ivan Reis
- Invisibles (v.2), 1998; 19 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.2), 1998; 20 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.2), 1999; 21 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.2), 1999; 22 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.3), 1999; 1 (Box 14)
  Artist/Penciler: Phillip Bond
  Notes: Vol. 3 published in reverse order, starting with #12
- Invisibles (v.3), 1999; 2 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.3), 1999; 3 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.3), 1999; 4 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.3), 1999; 5 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.3), 1999; 6 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.3), 2000; 7 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.3), 2000; 8 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.3), 2000; 9 (Box 14)
  Artist/Penciler: Philip Bond
- Invisibles (v.3), 2000; 10 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.3), 2000; 11 (Box 14)
- Invisibles (v.3), 2000; 12 (Box 14)
- Iron Man, 1984; Ann. 7 (Box 14)
  Author: Bob Harras
  Artist/Penciler: Luke McDonnell
- It Girl, 2002 (Box 14)
  Artist/Penciler: Chyna Clugston-Major
  Notes: Atomics one-shot spin-off
- Ithacon 17 program (Box 14)
  Notes: Program for Ithacon comic convention; irregular-size, 2 copies
- Jack Kirby's Fourth World, 1997; 2 (Box 14)
- Jenny Finn, 1999; 1 (Box 14)
  Notes: four issue mini-series series
- Jenny Finn, 1999; 2 (Box 14)
- Jenny Sparks, 2000; 1 (Box 15)
  Notes: Authority spin-off; five issue mini-series
- Jenny Sparks, 2000; 2 (Box 15)
- Jenny Sparks, 2000; 3 (Box 15)
- Jenny Sparks, 2000; 4 (Box 15)
- Jenny Sparks, 2000; 5 (Box 15)
- Jet, 2000; 1 (Box 15)
  Author: Dan Abnett, Andy Lanning
  Artist/Penciler: Dustin Nguyen
- Jet, 2000; 2 (Box 15)
- Jet, 2001; 3 (Box 15)
- Jet, 2001; 4 (Box 15)
- JLA, 1997; 1 (Box 15)
  Artist/Penciler: Howard Porter
- JLA, 1997; 2 (Box 15)
- JLA, 1997; 3 (Box 15)
- JLA, 1997; 4 (Box 15)
- JLA, 1997; 5 (Box 15)
- JLA, 1997; 6 (Box 15)
- JLA, 1997; 7 (Box 15)
- JLA, 1997; 8 (Box 15)
- JLA, 1997; 9 (Box 15)
- JLA, 1997; 10 (Box 15)
- JLA, 1997; 11 (Box 15)
- JLA, 1997; 12 (Box 15)
- JLA, 1998; 13 (Box 15)
- JLA, 1998; 14 (Box 15)
- JLA, 1998; 15 (Box 15)
- JLA, 1998; 16 (Box 15)
- JLA, 1998; 17 (Box 15)
  Artist/Penciler: Arnie Jorgensen
- JLA, 1998; 18 (Box 15)
- JLA, 1998; 19 (Box 15)
- JLA, 1998; 20 (Box 15)
- JLA, 1998; 21 (Box 15)
- JLA, 1998; 22 (Box 15)
- JLA, 1998; 23 (Box 15)
- JLA, 1998; 24 (Box 15)
- JLA, 1999; 25 (Box 15)
- JLA, 1999; 26 (Box 15)
- JLA, 1999; 27 (Box 15)
  Artist/Penciler: Mark Pajarillo
- JLA, 1999; 28 (Box 15)
- JLA, 1999; 29 (Box 15)
- JLA, 1999; 30 (Box 15)
- JLA, 1999; 31 (Box 15)
- JLA, 1999; 32 (Box 15)
- JLA, 1999; 33 (Box 15)
- JLA, 1999; 34 (Box 15)
- JLA, 1999; 35 (Box 15)
- JLA, 1999; 36 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2000; 37 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2000; 38 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2000; 39 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2000; 40 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2000; 41 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2000; 42 (Box 15)
  Author: Dan Curtis Johnson
- JLA, 2000; 43 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2000; 44 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2000; 45 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2000; 46 (Box 15)
  Artist/Penciler: Steve Scott
- JLA, 2000; 47 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2000; 48 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2001; 49 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2001; 50 (Box 15)
  Notes: 48 page special issue featuring multiple aritsts
- JLA, 2001; 51 (Box 15)
  Artist/Penciler: Mike S. Miller
- JLA, 2001; 52 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2001; 53 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2001; 54 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2001; 55 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2001; 56 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2001; 57 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2001; 58 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2001; 59 (Box 15)
  Author: Chuck Dixon, Scott Beatty
- JLA, 2001; 60 (Box 15)
  Artist/Penciler: Cliff Rathburn
- JLA, 2002; 61 (Box 15)
  Artist/Penciler: Doug Mahnke
- JLA, 2002; 62 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2002; 63 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2002; 64 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2002; 65 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2002; 66 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2002; 67 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2002; 68 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2002; 69 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2002; 70 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2002; 71 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2002; 72 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2002; 73 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2002; 74 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2003; 75 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2003; 76 (Box 15)
  Artist/Penciler: Lewis LaRosa
- JLA, 2003; 77 (Box 15)
  Artist/Penciler: Gary Banks
- JLA, 2003; 78 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2003; 79 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2003; 80 (Box 15)
  Artist/Penciler: Duncan Rouleau
- JLA, 2003; 81 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2003; 82 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2003; 83 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2003; 84 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2003; 85 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2003; 86 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2003; 87 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2003; 88 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2003; 89 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2004; 90 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2004; 91 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2004; 92 (Box 15)
  Author: Dennis O'neil
- JLA, 2004; 93 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2004; 94 (Box 15)
  Author: John Bryne
  Artist/Penciler: Chris Claremont
- JLA, 2004; 95 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2004; 96 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2005; 97 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2004; 98 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2004; 99 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2004; 100 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2004; 101 (Box 15)
  Author: Chuck Austen
  Artist/Penciler: Ron Garney
- JLA, 2004; 102 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2004; 107 (Box 15)
- JLA, 2004; 108 (Box 15)
- JLA, 1998; 1,000,000 (Box 15)
  Notes: Part of DC One Million event; published between 23 & 24(?)
- JLA, 1997; Ann. 1 (Box 15)
- JLA, 1999; Ann. 2 (Box 15)
  Artist/Penciler: Jason Orfalas
- JLA, 2000; Ann. 3 (Box 15)
  Author: Steve Scott
  Artist/Penciler: Brain K. Vaughn
- JLA 80-Page Giant, 1998; 1 (Box 15)
- JLA Classified, 2005; 1 (Box 15)
  Artist/Penciler: Ed McGuinness
- JLA in Crisis: Secret Files and Origins, 1998; 1 (Box 15)
- JLA/Avengers, 2003; 1 (Box 15)
- JLA/Avengers, 2003; 2 (Box 15)
- JLA/Avengers, 2003; 3 (Box 15)
- JLA/Avengers, 2003; 4 (Box 15)
- JLA/Haven: Arrival, 2001 (Box 15)
  Author: Ashley-Jayne Nicolaus, Matthew P. Schuster
- JLA/Titans, 1998; 1 (Box 15)
  Author: Devin Grayson
- JLA/Titans, 1998; 2 (Box 15)
- JLA/Titans, 1998; 3 (Box 15)
- JLA: Paradise Lost, 1998; 1 (Box 15)
- JLA: Paradise Lost, 1998; 2 (Box 15)
- JLA: Paradise Lost, 1998; 3 (Box 15)
- JLA: Secret Files, 1997; 1 (Box 15)
- JLA: Secret Files, 1998; 2 (Box 15)
- JLA: The Nail, 1998; 1 (Box 15)
  Artist/Penciler: Mark Farmer
  Notes: Cover title: Justice League: The Nail
- JLA: The Nail, 1998; 2 (Box 15)
- JLA: The Nail, 1998; 3 (Box 15)
- JLA: Tomorrow Woman, 1998; 1 (Box 15)
  Artist/Penciler: Yanick Paquette
  Notes: Part of Girlfrenzy crossover
- JLA: World Without Grown-Ups, 1998; 1 (Box 15)
  Author: Todd Dezago
  Artist/Penciler: Mike McKone, Humberto Ramos
- JLA: World Without Grown-Ups, 1998; 2 (Box 15)
- JLA: Year One, 1998; 1 (Box 15)
  Artist/Penciler: Barry Kitson
- JLA: Year One, 1998; 2 (Box 15)
- JLA: Year One, 1998; 3 (Box 15)
- JLA: Year One, 1998; 4 (Box 15)
- JLA: Year One, 1998; 5 (Box 15)
- JLA: Year One, 1998; 6 (Box 15)
- JLA: Year One, 1998; 7 (Box 15)
- JLA: Year One, 1998; 8 (Box 15)
- JLA: Year One, 1998; 9 (Box 15)
- JLA: Year One, 1998; 10 (Box 15)
- JLA: Year One, 1998; 11 (Box 15)
- JLA: Year One, 1998; 12 (Box 15)
- John Byrne's 2112, 1992 (Box 16)
- John Byrne's Next Men, 1992; 9 (Box 16)
- John Byrne's Next Men, 1992; 10 (Box 16)
- John Byrne's Next Men, 1992; 11 (Box 16)
- John Byrne's Next Men, 1993; 12 (Box 16)
- John Byrne's Next Men, 1993; 13 (Box 16)
- John Byrne's Next Men, 1993; 14 (Box 16)
- John Byrne's Next Men, 1993; 15 (Box 16)
- John Byrne's Next Men, 1993; 16 (Box 16)
- John Byrne's Next Men, 1993; 17 (Box 16)
- John Byrne's Next Men, 1993; 18 (Box 16)
- John Byrne's Next Men, 1993; 19 (Box 16)
- John Byrne's Next Men, 1993; 20 (Box 16)
- John Byrne's Next Men, 1993; 21 (Box 16)
  Notes: First appearance of Hellboy
- John Byrne's Next Men, 1993; 22 (Box 16)
- John Byrne's Next Men, 1993; 23 (Box 16)
- John Byrne's Next Men, 1994; 24 (Box 16)
- John Byrne's Next Men, 1994; 25 (Box 16)
- John Byrne's Next Men, 1994; 26 (Box 16)
- John Byrne's Next Men, 1994; 27 (Box 16)
- John Byrne's Next Men, 1994; 28 (Box 16)
- John Byrne's Next Men, 1994; 29 (Box 16)
- John Byrne's Next Men, 1994; 30 (Box 16)
- JSA, 1999; 1 (Box 16)
  Artist/Penciler: Steve Sadowski
- JSA, 1999; 2 (Box 16)
- JSA, 1999; 3 (Box 16)
- JSA, 1999; 4 (Box 16)
- JSA, 1999; 5 (Box 16)
- JSA, 2000; 6 (Box 16)
  Author: David Goyer
- JSA, 2000; 7 (Box 16)
- JSA, 2000; 8 (Box 16)
- JSA, 2000; 9 (Box 16)
- JSA, 2000; 10 (Box 16)
- JSA, 2000; 11 (Box 16)
  Artist/Penciler: Buzz
- JSA, 2000; 12 (Box 16)
- JSA, 2000; 13 (Box 16)
- JSA, 2000; 14 (Box 16)
- JSA, 2000; 15 (Box 16)
- JSA, 2000; 16 (Box 16)
- Junior Carrot Patrol, 1989; 1 (Box 16)
  Notes: Flaming Carrot spin-off
- Junior Carrot Patrol, 1989; 2 (Box 16)
- Junk Culture, 1997; 1 (Box 16)
  Notes: two issue limited series
- Junk Culture, 1997; 2 (Box 16)
- Justice League America, 1994; 0 (Box 16)
  Author: Gerard Jones
  Artist/Penciler: Chuck Wojtkiewicz
  Notes: Zero Hour crossover, published before #93
- Justice League America, 1992; 68 (Box 16)
  Author: Dan Jurgens
  Artist/Penciler: Rick Burchett
- Justice League America, 1992; 69 (Box 16)
- Justice League America, 1993; 71 (Box 16)
- Justice League America, 1993; 72 (Box 16)
- Justice League America, 1993; 73 (Box 16)
- Justice League America, 1993; 74 (Box 16)
- Justice League America, 1994; 75 (Box 16)
- Justice League America, 1994; 93 (Box 16)
- Justice League America, 1994; 94 (Box 16)
- Justice League America, 1994; 95 (Box 16)
- Justice League America, 1995; 96 (Box 16)
  Artist/Penciler: Randy Green
- Justice League America, 1995; 97 (Box 16)
- Justice League America, 1995; 98 (Box 16)
- Justice League America, 1995; 99 (Box 16)
- Justice League America, 1995; 100 (Box 16)
- Justice League Elite, 2004; 1 (Box 16)
  Author: Joe Kelly
- Justice League Elite, 2004; 2 (Box 16)
- Justice League Elite, 2004; 3 (Box 16)
- Justice League Elite, 2004; 4 (Box 16)
- Justice League Elite, 2004; 5 (Box 16)
- Justice League Europe, 1992; 44 (Box 16)
  Artist/Penciler: Ron Randall
- Justice League Europe, 1992; 45 (Box 16)
- Justice League Europe, 1993; 46 (Box 16)